CONTACT

786-914-0778

https://sarjohnson.github.io/portfolio-website

https://linkedin.com/in/sarahjohnson-dev/

Sej17b@my.fsu.edu

Winter Haven, FL Open to Remote

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development Completed 02/2024

- Intensive project-based online training program with a focus on JavaScript, React, Python, and much more.
- Developed 7 web applications, a phone application, and an API using various languages, frameworks, and libraries.
- View repositories here:
 https://github.com/SarJohnson

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- MONGODB
- NODE.JS
- REACT
- BOOTSTRAP
- ANGULAR
- NOSQL
- SQL
- PYTHON
- DJANGO
- AWS
- MICROSOFT SUITE
- GOOGLE SUITE
- ORA
- GIT
- POSTMAN

SARAH JOHNSON

Web Developer

OVERVIEW

A web developer with a unique blend of artistic passion and engineering expertise, adept at web development. Backed by a background in customer service and administrative roles, excelling in computer proficiency, data interpretation, problemsolving, and collaborative work.

PROJECTS

HorrorFlix

- Created a nonrelational database of horror movies from several subgenres.
- Built an API with using Node.js and Mongoose to pull from this database.
- Developed a website using React that allows users to find horror movies to watch and save their favorites to their profile.
- Tested with Postman and deployed with Heroku.

Make 'Em Eat Recipe App

- Built a website using Django that allows users to view family recipes, see information for each recipe, view tables according to difficulty level, and read family stories.
- Deployed to Heroku and used AWS for media file storage.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Empyrean Benefits Solution Benefits Administrator 09/2021–05/2023

 Utilized problem solving skills along with active listening and multi-tasking to assist customers with their benefits, leave, and payroll.

GEICO Administrative Assistant

10/2020-09/2021

- Refined administrative work such as calendar maintenance, inventory and ordering, expense management, scheduling, payroll, and office management with Microsoft Excel.
- Demonstrated successful time management by also assisting with reception, customer service, policy change processing, and customer retention program management.

Jersey Mikes Assistant Manager

04/2019-10/2020

- Oversaw my team with duties such as inventory and ordering, shift and schedule management, employee training, shift leading supervision, and customer service.
- Demonstrated exemplary leadership, collaboration, and team building.